{
  "apikey": "%PUT-YOUR-API-KEY-HERE%",
  "description": "This is simple calibration data used for testing purposes. Do not use it in production environment!",
  "copyright": "Copyright (C) 2238 by BanAN Technologies Inc.",
  "test-data": [
    {
      "question": "72 + 63",
      "answer": 135
    },
    {
      "question": "85 + 11",
      "answer": 96
    },
    {
      "question": "61 + 89",
      "answer": 150
    },
    {
      "question": "21 + 29",
      "answer": 50
    },
    {
      "question": "26 + 72",
      "answer": 98
    },
    {
      "question": "27 + 5",
      "answer": 32
    },
    {
      "question": "82 + 96",
      "answer": 178
    },
    {
      "question": "5 + 85",
      "answer": 90
    },
    {
      "question": "79 + 42",
      "answer": 121
    },
    {
      "question": "44 + 8",
      "answer": 52
    },
    {
      "question": "72 + 64",
      "answer": 136
    },
    {
      "question": "26 + 54",
      "answer": 80
    },
    {
      "question": "2 + 80",
      "answer": 82
    },
    {
      "question": "16 + 16",
      "answer": 32
    },
    {
      "question": "26 + 29",
      "answer": 55
    },
    {
      "question": "2 + 54",
      "answer": 56
    },
    {
      "question": "95 + 72",
      "answer": 167
    },
    {
      "question": "39 + 18",
      "answer": 57
    },
    {
      "question": "32 + 47",
      "answer": 79
    },
    {
      "question": "77 + 6",
      "answer": 83
    },
    {
      "question": "93 + 24",
      "answer": 117
    },
    {
      "question": "97 + 9",
      "answer": 106
    },
    {
      "question": "10 + 7",
      "answer": 17
    },
    {
      "question": "83 + 48",
      "answer": 131
    },
    {
      "question": "98 + 40",
      "answer": 138
    },
    {
      "question": "29 + 75",
      "answer": 104
    },
    {
      "question": "3 + 16",
      "answer": 19
    },
    {
      "question": "56 + 31",
      "answer": 87
    },
    {
      "question": "23 + 2",
      "answer": 25
    },
    {
      "question": "44 + 62",
      "answer": 106
    },
    {
      "question": "66 + 95",
      "answer": 161
    },
    {
      "question": "19 + 31",
      "answer": 52
    },
    {
      "question": "74 + 52",
      "answer": 126
    },
    {
      "question": "19 + 49",
      "answer": 68
    },
    {
      "question": "24 + 83",
      "answer": 107
    },
    {
      "question": "15 + 57",
      "answer": 72
    },
    {
      "question": "32 + 26",
      "answer": 58
    },
    {
      "question": "28 + 6",
      "answer": 34
    },
    {
      "question": "89 + 100",
      "answer": 189
    },
    {
      "question": "56 + 60",
      "answer": 116
    },
    {
      "question": "100 + 61",
      "answer": 161
    },
    {
      "question": "57 + 12",
      "answer": 69
    },
    {
      "question": "2 + 74",
      "answer": 76
    },
    {
      "question": "59 + 28",
      "answer": 87
    },
    {
      "question": "64 + 28",
      "answer": 92
    },
    {
      "question": "53 + 85",
      "answer": 138
    },
    {
      "question": "12 + 11",
      "answer": 23
    },
    {
      "question": "31 + 92",
      "answer": 123
    },
    {
      "question": "75 + 22",
      "answer": 97
    },
    {
      "question": "34 + 48",
      "answer": 82
    },
    {
      "question": "21 + 76",
      "answer": 97
    },
    {
      "question": "86 + 26",
      "answer": 112
    },
    {
      "question": "4 + 17",
      "answer": 21
    },
    {
      "question": "14 + 48",
      "answer": 62
    },
    {
      "question": "55 + 82",
      "answer": 137
    },
    {
      "question": "28 + 71",
      "answer": 99
    },
    {
      "question": "79 + 45",
      "answer": 124
    },
    {
      "question": "34 + 60",
      "answer": 94
    },
    {
      "question": "96 + 57",
      "answer": 153
    },
    {
      "question": "56 + 5",
      "answer": 61
    },
    {
      "question": "68 + 85",
      "answer": 153
    },
    {
      "question": "35 + 89",
      "answer": 124
    },
    {
      "question": "71 + 71",
      "answer": 142
    },
    {
      "question": "19 + 63",
      "answer": 82
    },
    {
      "question": "16 + 84",
      "answer": 100
    },
    {
      "question": "70 + 14",
      "answer": 84
    },
    {
      "question": "57 + 87",
      "answer": 144
    },
    {
      "question": "88 + 4",
      "answer": 92
    },
    {
      "question": "51 + 59",
      "answer": 110
    },
    {
      "question": "69 + 80",
      "answer": 149
    },
    {
      "question": "48 + 78",
      "answer": 126
    },
    {
      "question": "84 + 99",
      "answer": 183
    },
    {
      "question": "41 + 22",
      "answer": 63
    },
    {
      "question": "5 + 4",
      "answer": 9
    },
    {
      "question": "43 + 100",
      "answer": 143
    },
    {
      "question": "29 + 62",
      "answer": 91
    },
    {
      "question": "86 + 36",
      "answer": 122
    },
    {
      "question": "73 + 63",
      "answer": 136
    },
    {
      "question": "89 + 87",
      "answer": 176
    },
    {
      "question": "76 + 48",
      "answer": 124
    },
    {
      "question": "18 + 71",
      "answer": 89
    },
    {
      "question": "40 + 44",
      "answer": 84
    },
    {
      "question": "70 + 55",
      "answer": 125
    },
    {
      "question": "9 + 30",
      "answer": 39
    },
    {
      "question": "87 + 91",
      "answer": 178
    },
    {
      "question": "21 + 43",
      "answer": 64
    },
    {
      "question": "48 + 23",
      "answer": 71
    },
    {
      "question": "21 + 58",
      "answer": 79
    },
    {
      "question": "76 + 13",
      "answer": 89
    },
    {
      "question": "97 + 37",
      "answer": 134
    },
    {
      "question": "100 + 36",
      "answer": 136
    },
    {
      "question": "40 + 88",
      "answer": 128
    },
    {
      "question": "96 + 82",
      "answer": 178
    },
    {
      "question": "84 + 16",
      "answer": 100
    },
    {
      "question": "56 + 70",
      "answer": 126
    },
    {
      "question": "19 + 100",
      "answer": 119
    },
    {
      "question": "98 + 7",
      "answer": 105
    },
    {
      "question": "90 + 87",
      "answer": 177
    },
    {
      "question": "30 + 73",
      "answer": 103
    },
    {
      "question": "98 + 52",
      "answer": 150
    }
  ],
  "chunk": {
    "number": 3,
    "total": 22,
    "size": 100,
    "range": {
      "from": 200,
      "to": 300
    }
  }
}